Nathan Sorkin

FULL STACK DEVELOPER

I'm a full stack developer in NYC with a passion for building great experiences. My focuses are in React, JavaScript / Node, HTML, and CSS/SCSS, but I am always trying to learn new things to expand my skill set and reach my goals of leading a dev team.

www.nathansorkin.com hello@nathansorkin.com (330)-907-9390 Brooklyn, NY

WORK EXPERIENCE

Full Stack Developer
Locusview
May 2020 - Current

- Working closely with a small tight-knit team to fulfill client feature requests at a rapid pace while still focusing on performance and code clarity
- Implemented new coding practices such as JSDoc, Typescript, ESLint, and Prettier as well as bringing a focus to DRY coding standards.
- Implemented better testing practices using Chai / Mocha which greatly improved our ability to catch bugs. This paired with the code refactoring lead to much faster turnaround times on any issues.

Front End Developer

March 2019 - March 2020

b8ta

- Took initiative to create Node scripts that reduced client and employee workload by converting b8ta's CMS data into
 easily managed CSV's as well as allowing the user to feed a CSV into the CMS for easy data management and less
 manual input.
- Communicated directly with clients to discover needs, answer questions surrounding the application and discuss updates as well as our product road map.
- Worked with clients such as Nike, Bonobos, Bluemercury, and others to seamlessly integrate our store locator application into their e-commerce platforms while maintaining the integrity of their style guides.
- Oversaw the agile process as scrum master for each weekly sprint, and helped prioritize work to ensure it aligned with company goals and client road maps.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Developer Certificate Bloc

September 2017 - October 2018

Bloc is a self driven development bootcamp that uses projects to build out your knowledge and give you an idea of real world applications. Using a mentor system available to students for help, and support for any questions. Broadening and strengthening my skill set in HTML, CSS, Javascript, React, Ruby, Rails, Git, and Node.

SKILLS

- Javascript, HTML, CSS, CSS-in-JS, SCSS, React, Typescript, Node, Git, Python
- · Interpersonal Communication, Problem Solving, Project Planning, Time Management

TOOLS

VSCode, Jira, Figma, Sketch, InDesign, Zeplin, Github